

Riga, Latvia

□ (+371) 29969608 | ■ thewwworm@gmail.com | • thewwworm | • the thewworm | • the thewworm | • the thewworm | • the thewworm | • the

"There is no black magic in JS"



Summary_

C.T.Co

Current Lead Software Developer at C.t.co. 6+ years of experience in software development. Loves Javascript on both - frotnend and backend. Cares about the things he is working on and enjoys seeing them imporve. Enjoys solving complex tasks and trying on new things. Has an opinion that Javascript is not black magic and infact can be understood by mere human being.

Work Experience _____

Riga, Latvia Nov. 2018 - Now

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER · Worked as the stream leading frontend developer on the reassurance application(Angular/Redux)

- Worked on frontend(React/Redux) of project management application
- · Conducted interviews for promotions and recruitment's

LPB Bank Riga, Latvia

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Dec. 2016 - Nov. 2018

- Worked on frontend(Jquery) and backend(Node.js/Express/MySql) of banks website.
- · Worked on frontend(Jquery) side of the website for used by merchants for payment management
- · Developed multiple side applications using Node.js on the backend and React/Redux on the frontend

DNB Bank Riga, Latvia

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

· Worked on supporting multiple bank applications using Js(Jquery) and OpenEdge ABL

Self Riga, Latvia

· Works on pet projects, such as making games in Unity, writing NPM modules and in general trying out new experimenting writing code

About me_

Interested in many things in the world and always excited to learn more. Enjoys programming as work and as a hobby as well. Loves reading books, long walks and visiting new places, also has a great fun tinkering with computers in general.

Education

Progmeistars courses Riga Latvia

HAS ATTENDED

Before starting work

Jun. 2014 - Dec. 2016

• multiple courses on the basics of the programming.

Extra_

Languages

- · Russian native
- · English C1
- · Latvian A2

Work Expectations

- Full time
- Frontend and/or backend JS work
- 3700€+ after tax salary